[
        {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Tuvo",
        "Back": "Had"
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Algo",
        "Back": "something"
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Pues",
        "Back": "well"
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Ademas",
        "Back": "also"
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "llevar",
        "Back": "to carry"
    },   {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Podemos intentarlo",
        "Back": "we can try"
        
    },    {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Que emocion",
        "Back": "what a thrill"
    
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Bromeando",
        "Back": "Joking"
    
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Digo",
        "Back": "Say"

    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Piensa",
        "Back": "Think"

    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "No se que le vas a regalar",
        "Back": "I dont know what you are going to give him"
        
    },   {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Casi se mi olvida",
        "Back": "I almost forgot"

    },   {  
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "No seas asi",
        "Back": "Dont be like that "      
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Sobrino",
        "Back": "Nephew"

    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "llevare",
        "Back": "I will take"

    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Reconoce",
        "Back": "Recognize"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Entrenamiento",
        "Back": "Training"

    },   {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Cancha",
        "Back": "Court"

    },    {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Prestar",
        "Back": "To lend"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "relajate",
        "Back": "relax"

    },  {
        "Category": "Spanish",
        "Front": "Equivocado",
        "Back": "Wrong"
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "What does DOM mean",
        "Back": "Document Object Model"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Arabic",
        "Front": "أزرق",
        "Back": "Blue"
        
    },   {
        "Category": "Arabic",
        "Front": "امرأة",
        "Back": "Woman"
        
    },   {
        "Category": "Arabic",
        "Front": "أستاذ",
        "Back": "The professor"
    },    {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "What does JSON stand for",
        "Back": "JavaScript Object Notation"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "What is a DDoS attack",
        "Back": "attempts to exhaust an applications resources. The perpetrators behind these attacks flood a site with errant traffic, resulting in poor website functionality or knocking it offline altogether"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "JavaScript ",
        "Front": "What does .map do",
        "Back": "Creates a copy of an array and alters it however we state"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Arabic",
        "Front": "زوجة",
        "Back": "wife"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what is routing",
        "Back": ""
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "what is an API",
        "Back": "Application Programming Interface... A source for some external data that you can use in your application"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what is fetching?",
        "Back": "the retrieval of data by a software program, script, or hardware device"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "what does the fetch() method return",
        "Back": "Returns a Promise so you can use the then() and catch() methods to handle it"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what is a response?",
        "Back": "when a search engine or website visitor makes a request to a web server, a three digit HTTP Response Status Code is returned. This code indi
                indicates what is about to happen. A response code of 200 means - okay, here is the content you requested. 301 means - the page has moved, redirecting you now."
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "asynchronous code",
        "Back": "refers to the occurrence of events independent of the main program flow. events do no wait for others to finish."
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what does axios do",
        "Back": ""
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "why use MongoDB",
        "Back": "Everything stored in MongoDB is a JSON object...JavaScript Object Notation"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what is an ORM",
        "Back": "Object Relational Mapper ex - Mongoose (allows us to communicate with MongoDB using javascript)"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "what does CORS stand for ",
        "Back": "Cross Origin Resource Sharing"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what are the 2 ports in use ?",
        "Back": ".3000 for the front end(react) and 8000 for backend(apis etc)"
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "asynchronous code",
        "Back": "refers to the occurrence of events independent of the main program flow. events do no wait for others to finish."
        
    },  {
        "Category": "Coding",
        "Front": "what does axios do",
        "Back": ""
        
    },  {
        "Category": "coding",
        "Front": "why use MongoDB",
        "Back": "Everything stored in MongoDB is a JSON object"
        
    }

]